https://www.kellogg.ox.ac.uk/privacy/

Privacy policies
Home » Privacy policies
Data protection
Kellogg College is part of the University of Oxford and conducts its operations in compliance with the University privacy policy.
The College obtains and uses large amounts of personal information about our students, alumni, staff, contractors, research participants and other individuals that come into contact with us. This information is defined as personal data in the General Data Protection Regulation and Data Protection Act 2018 and is often also referred to as Personal Information. Any action carried out which relates to personal information is known as processing.
The College is the Data Controller for the personal information it processes and we process this information for a variety of reasons in order to carry out our academic, employer, charitable, and other administrative functions. We aim to be as transparent as possible about the ways we use personal information; to only collect and retain the minimum amount of data possible and to keep it securely.
You can find out more information about the way we use personal information and the rights individuals have to control and manage their data from these web pages, and from the individual website privacy notices for Applicants, Students, Staff, and Alumni, Donors and Supporters.
General and online privacy policy
Read the policy
Applicant privacy policy
Read the policy
Student privacy policy
Read the policy
Alumni, Donors, and Supporters Privacy Policy
Read the policy
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Okay, thank you
